Summary.

A self-motivated developer with 2+ years of experience in a fast-paced leading educational startup and continuously striving to expand skill sets. Proficient in Python/Django and learning new programming languages like Golang. Aspiring to be part of a team that solves problems using technology and learn new things. Have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science.

Technical Skills

Operating Systems GNU/Linux (Ubuntu, Arch Linux), Windows

Programming Python, Go(Basics),

Web HTML, CSS

Frameworks Django, Flask(Basics)

Version Control System Gi

Experience

Entri.me Ernakulam, Kerala

PRODUCT ENGINEER Feb. 2015 - Present

Feb. 2015 - Present

Recursive Labs Ernakulam, Kerala

SOFTWARE TRAINEE March. 2014 - Jan. 2015

Feb. 2015 - Present

Projects

Mvaayoo Python

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JOSEJIBIN/MVAAYOO-PYTHON

• Python wrapper around Mvaayoo API

URL Shortener

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JOSEJIBIN/URL-SHORTENER

- A simple URL shortener application
- Written using the Django framework
- Ability to create custom short URLs

Hercule

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JOSEJIBIN/HERCULE

- · A minimalist, responsive, and open-source theme for Hugo, a fast static site generator built with GoLang
- A minimal blog theme
- Built-in support for 404 pages, Disqus comments, and Google Analytics.

Volunteer Experience

Django Girls Workshop

Содсь

Django Girls is a community that empowers and helps women to organize free, one-day programming workshop for 30-60 people about building their first application using HTML, CSS, Python and Django.

coached Django Girls Thiruvananthapuram event organized by students from LBSITW

Education

Lourdes Matha College of Science and Technology

Kerala University

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering

Mar. 2009 - 2013

• Organised inter college computer science fest